{
    "subject": "resource/Back_to_Back_(Status_Quo_album)",
    "predicate": "property/artist",
    "object": "resource/Status_Quo_(band)",
    "human_readable": "The artist of 'Back to Back' album is Status Quo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9821546077728271,
            "question": "Is 'Back to Back' an album by Status Quo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8011885285377502,
            "question": "Which artist produced the album 'Back to Back'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.786616861820221,
            "question": "Who is the artist behind the 'Back to Back' album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.771087110042572,
            "question": "What is the name of the album released by Status Quo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7360560894012451,
            "question": "Name a famous album by Status Quo."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7299068570137024,
            "question": "Who are the creators of the 'Back to Back' album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6136892437934875,
            "question": "Can you tell me an album title by Status Quo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5608755946159363,
            "question": "Which band created the album 'Back to Back'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37390872836112976,
            "question": "What musical work is associated with Status Quo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3409399688243866,
            "question": "What is the name of the band that released 'Back to Back'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The artist of 'Back to Back' album is Status Quo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2831_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical work is associated with Status Quo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2831_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which band created the album 'Back to Back'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2831_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me an album title by Status Quo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2831_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2831_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2831_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2831_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2831_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2831_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2831_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2831_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2831_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2831_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2831_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents mention \"Status Quo\" as the band name, and there are references to their albums such as \"Back To Back (1983 UK 10-track LP)\". This supports the statement that the artist of the 'Back to Back' album is Status Quo."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}